Twilight. You have changed.
By being in the Forger household,
you've developed unnecessary emotions.
You lack the sharpness that is required
of a spy.
Right now, you're just like
a knife with a chipped blade.
Seeing you in that state pains me.
Oh…
But I like that gentle side of him too.
My heart is beating so fast
that it's painful. I love you.
Even if you become a toy knife
that retracts on contact,
I will still love and admire you.
In fact, seeing that cute side of you
will make me love you even more.
But things can't continue this way.
Drawing out that cute side of him
is a duty that I alone must fulfill.
Yor Forger.
I must usurp the wife's position
from that woman.
MISSION 22:
UNDERGROUND TENNIS TOURNAMENT CAMPBELLDON
ORIGINAL WORK BY TATSUYA ENDO
SERIALIZED ON SHUEISHA'S SHONEN JUMP PLUS
Cavi Campbell, 56 years old.
He obtained his fortune
in the energy industry,
and he's also well-known
as an antique art collector.
He owns a painting that is worth
one million dalc.
It's called "Lady in the Sun."
That's our next target.
A painting?
The original owner of the painting
was the late Colonel Erik Zacharis.
An intelligence officer
in the Eastern Army during the war,
and he played a key role
in ending the war.
Yes, and he possessed
damaging classified information that
he refused to make public
because he knew it would
reignite the flames of war.
It's known as the Zacharis Dossier.
It's believed that these documents include
human subject research in the East,
and the massacre of prisoners of war
in the East. But the details are unclear.
For a while it was called
the unexploded ordnance
and no one knew about its whereabouts.
The clue to locating that dossier
is in that painting?
The information is from a trusted source.
There is most likely a code
hidden in that painting.
It's only a matter of time before
Campbell or the Eastern government
learns of this secret.
Our mission is to retrieve
the Zacharis Dossier before anyone else.
Even if the information
is damaging to both the East and West,
it will no doubt instigate conflict
if it ever becomes public.
Where is the painting being kept?
It's in the basement of the Campbell house
with the rest of his art collection.
But the security is tight and they have a
connection with the State Security Service
so anyone that has tried to force
their way in has been disposed of.
Infiltrating that building
will be quite risky.
Do you have a plan?
Of course, preparation is underway.
Come on!
Game set!
You've got to be kidding me!
Give me back my money!
The payout for this match is…
The betting for the next game
will close in ten minutes.
Nightfall…
What is it, Twilight?
Wasn't there any other option for us?
I believe this is the best option we have.
Campbell and members
of the underworld tennis club organize
the underground tennis tournament,
called the Campbelldon. It's an illicit
event where huge amounts of money
flow from big shots of the financial world
and underworld figures.
Normally, players in the tournament
are supported by the wealthy members,
but the general public
can also enter the game by paying
an expensive entrance fee.
And as a prize, the winner is given
one item they want
from Campbell's art collection.
But why tennis?
What's the underworld tennis club?
I guess they really love tennis.
As long as we win, our mission is
accomplished. No risks involved.
I hope it's as easy as it sounds.
The fourth match of round one
will now begin. It's the Twain
and Nafalia Phony team!
It's our turn.
Apparently they're a married couple.
You'll get killed!
-Get out of here!
-I bet on their divorce!
Why did you choose this cover?
Wow… all these people
think that we're a married couple!
Their opponent is
the Walson and Bobble team!
They're the legendary duo
who won the Grand Slam ten years ago!
Whoa.
They're retired professional players!
Do you have experience playing tennis?
I dabbled with it a bit.
I practiced a little at home too.
That's unfair!
Anya wants to play tennis too!
Then let's all play together.
What did you tell your family?
I told them that I have a tennis match
with some important figures
in the medical field.
I see.
Soon, you won't have to
make excuses like that anymore.
Well, don't worry.
You can stay huddled up in the corner.
With this mission, you'll come to see
that I'm the perfect person
to play your wife
for Operation Strix.
I'll defeat them on my own…
So you can count on me, Twilight!
Nightfall is so eager for success
that she's becoming rash.
Keep an eye on her to keep her in check.
This mission is such a hassle.
The odds are 40 to 1.3!
Is there anyone courageous enough
to bet on the dark horse?
It seems like we're being taken
very lightly.
Are they lost tourists who wandered
their way in here?
Even after we retired,
we continued to search for ways
to master our tennis skills.
After searching for the most
challenging opponents,
we found this underground tournament.
In order to play here today,
we went into the mountains
and endured grueling training.
Well, let's all do our best
and have a great game.
A game? How ridiculous.
What you'll experience,
is complete devastation.
Phony's serve.
Fifteen-love.
An ace against a professional player!
Just as I expected of you, Twilight!
You redefined the meaning of "dabbled."
I love you.
Thirty-love.
Forty-love.
Game, set.
What was that?
I've never seen a serve like that
even from a top ranking player.
Damn it. Aim at that woman.
Take that.
All right!
Love-15!
What was that?
Not bad, Night… Nafalia.
He praised me!
That was only the beginning.
All right. While I keep showing off
my cool self,
I'll smash the enemies in seconds,
quickly get the painting, and…
Nightfall, you're amazing!
Be my doubles partner for life!
Oh my, Twilight!
Oh…
Game set! Won by the Phony team!
This is a major upset!
The amateur couple
shut out and won against
the professionals!
It's the birth of
an incredible dark horse!
Was this game just pure luck?
This tournament just became unpredictable!
That was splendid!
These developments could bring in
lots of money.
You can't plan any fixed matches,
Mr. Campbell.
I just want to simply enjoy watching
and making bets on tennis.
That was nothing but a match against
mediocre players.
Their next match is against my
Bolic Brothers. Their luck will run dry.
Your players are just drug addicts.
They're a little different this time.
We teamed up with the government
in preparation for
the East-West Sports Competition,
to create a new doping agent
called "OSO-R."
They will be using that this time.
Thanks for waiting!
Now we will begin the second round!
The first match
will be the Phony team,
who just displayed a miraculous game,
versus the Bolic team,
the rabid dogs of Dressen!
Nightfall, didn't you say that
there would be no risks involved?
Let's do our best… Darling.
Mother, can you get the ball?
Mother!
I'm sorry, Anya.
Mother, are you spaced out?
N… no, not at all!
A tennis tournament with his colleagues
at work,
means that she'll be there too?
I wonder what her relationship is
with Loid.
Oh no, what if I have to
revert back to the lifestyle that would
cause Yuri to worry?
The ball…
If that's bound to happen,
should I just get rid of her…
No! You mustn't!
Yor, you'll be punished
for having such thoughts!
It's okay, Mother.
You have nothing to worry about.
About what?
Can she read my thoughts?
It's okay. Father will win
and bring back a big prize.
Oh…
You're right. Loid can do anything, huh?
No matter who his opponent is,
he'll smash them!
Smash!
I'll kill you. In this game of tennis.
Nightfall…
This is not the Bolic Brothers
that we saw in round one.
I failed to mention this earlier,
but in this tournament, customized rackets
and equipment, doping, foul play,
and everything else is allowed.
They must be using muscle enhancing drugs.
They're enhancing it way too much.
Get them, you giants!
-I placed all my money on you guys!
-Lose, and you die!
I'll kill you.
Hey!
Whoa! Catan, the younger brother,
ripped the fence!
-I'll kill you!
-Just shut up and watch!
That's some superhuman strength!
The bets are about to close.
The miraculous Phony couple,
and the super powered Bolic Brothers.
-Who will win?
-Humans can't win against them!
Their power will no doubt
be a hassle to deal with.
How should I fight while
preserving my strength?
Whoa!
Now Anan, the older brother,
easily crushed the tennis ball!
Let's treat our equipment with care!
Hey, little boy.
You smell like you peed in your pants.
If you leaked in your pants,
have that woman change your diapers.
You leaked! Change your diapers!
I'll change it.
What? Cat got your tongue?
You're such a chicken.
Brother, he's dumb.
He doesn't know how to speak!
You're right!
He looks like he has no brains!
I bet he's lived a happy life
without a care in the world.
Game set. Won by…
-The Phony team.
-Give me back my money!
They're the real deal!
This couple's power is the real deal!
The Bolic Brothers were beaten!
They didn't stand a chance!
-Wow, that was a terrifying…
-Those dumb macho idiots!
game by the Phony couple.
You didn't have to hit them
that hard with your smashes.
My hand slipped.
They deserved it.
They were my trump card!
It seems like your drug
has room for improvement.
But that team sure is strong.
Isn't your team in danger too, Campbell?
Hm… Well…
Let's see about that.
After that, due to Nightfall's
unnecessarily daring
-and flashy moves, the Phony team
-How am I doing, Twilight?
-continued marching forward,
and they advanced
all the way to the finals.
Now, please wait here
for about 20 minutes until
the final match.
We only have one more match left.
Twilight, what did you think of
my super powerful
playing style? Well? How was it?
The final match is against
Campbell's son and daughter.
Both of them are still in high school,
but they've been receiving training
ever since they were little.
Since their father is the organizer,
let's be careful, keeping in mind that
he can pull dirty tricks.
Judging by their previous matches,
their skills are not that impressive.
I'll end the match in seconds.
And he'll ask me to become
his doubles partner for life!
-Nightfall.
-Twilight.
No way! Already? And here of all places?
Twilight, I'm not ready yet!
Don't push yourself too hard.
You're in bad shape.
Our opponents are tough. I know you're
feeling restless, but keep calm.
This isn't a problem at all.
Let's just get back to our mission…
I've heard many of my comrades say that,
only for them to die.
Once a spy loses his cool, that's the end.
I've taught you that over and over again.
I understand.
Twilight… you used to say
that we spies are expendable.
But you're worrying about me!
This is so unfair, Twilight.
You're such a player.
I love you.
Whoa! She's glaring at me!
Is she that unhappy with
the way I do things?
Damn it! I pulled my hand away from his.
I'm such an idiot.
I can still feel the tingling warmth
of Twilight's touch…
Tingling?
Don't tell me…
Twilight.
Hold your breath and close your eyes,
Nightfall.
It's a colorless and odorless
non-lethal chemical agent of some sort.
I see.
This is why all of the sibling's opponents
seemed out of shape.
It must be their objective to weaken us.
They're playing dirty.
It's locked from the outside.
I can easily pick the lock,
but there may be guards outside.
We must behave like normal citizens.
Let's pretend like
we fell into their trap.
Just in case, let's cover up
as much as we can
and climb on top of the lockers.
Can you still hold your breath?
Yes, for about ten minutes.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
thank you for waiting!
Now we will begin the final match of
the 14th Campbelldon Tournament!
The Phony Couple versus
the Campbell Siblings!
Will the Phony team be able to
stop the siblings
-from becoming third time champions?
-20,000 for the couple!
The odds are in favor of the siblings,
but only by a little!
Good. This is exactly as planned.
Everyone should bet on the couple.
This is exciting! I'll place my bet
on that couple too!
Me too.
Mr. Campbell, you're going to bet
on your children, right?
Of course. I bet ten million on my kids.
I'll take all the profit.
I doused them in that gas
for a good ten minutes.
You guys are looking a little pale.
Are you guys okay?
All right, Carrol and Kim.
Destroy them to your heart's content.
How are you feeling?
I still feel a little numb.
My pulse and breathing is a bit off.
I got a message from Dad.
He said that we no longer have to pretend
like we're struggling.
How annoying. Is he our acting director
or what? Let's get this over with,
and have him buy us a new cruiser.
Phony's serve.
What an easy ball.
Out.
There it is! Carrol's jet racket!
Don't say that this is unfair.
Learning how to use this
required training on our part.
The Phony team is looking good.
Will Kim not be able to reach that?
That totally exploded! The whip racket!
They're no big deal.
-The Campbell siblings are proving that…
-That's right! Get them!
-they are truly the champions!
-Carrol!
Game, Campbell.
The first set was won by
the Campbell siblings.
This is the first set the Phony team
has lost during this tournament!
Hey! Play harder!
You should've used the crosscourt shot,
you idiot!
You can do it, Nafalia.
I'll remember the faces of every single
person who badmouthed Twilight.
I'm sorry.
Now we're onto the second set.
The Phony team needs to
win this set no matter what.
The game starts with Carrol's serve…
-He returned it!
-That's so weak. But…
The ball is spinning.
That was just pure luck.
Love-30!
The Phony couple's
lackluster hits are
starting to regain power!
Damn it. What's happening?
Oh no, the Campbell team
has lost three games already!
Now it's time for…
Will the Phony team
win four consecutive games?
Oh, what was that?
Nafalia's ball went wayward!
I see. I was curious about
the 36 grooves within this court.
Now I know what they're for.
They most likely have other tricks
up their sleeves. It's troublesome.
It's no problem.
I don't plan on losing
to some petty tricks.
That's right.
Nafalia, observe your surroundings,
and be my backup support.
This is the reason why
I always admired Twilight.
That's why I chased after him,
and wanted to be next to him.
Admiration turned to love, and his dream
became my dream. In other words…
Stop spouting nonsense, Twilight.
I will fight with you,
and kick their asses.
I love you.
MISSION 23: THE UNSHAKEN PATH
Subtitle translation by: Lili Morita